ibuzzle.com 2018-09-28

# iBuzzle Privacy Policy

At iBuzzle.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Please read our privacy policy carefully. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by iBuzzle.com. Use of our Website assumes you have read, understood, and have agreed with our privacy policy. 

For the purpose of this privacy policy, "you" and "your" refers to any visitor of iBuzzle.com, "user" refers to a non-registered visitor of iBuzzle.com, and "member" refers to a registered visitor of iBuzzle.com. "We" and "us" refers to the staff of iBuzzle.com. "Outside parties" and "third-party advertisers" refers to individuals and organizations not owned or operated by iBuzzle.com. 

**Responsibility of Use**  
iBuzzle.com is not responsible for user information collected by outside parties while visiting iBuzzle.com. This includes information you voluntarily disclose through the use of forums, chats and e-mail, and information obtained through the use of links on our Website. 

**Consensual Use**  
If iBuzzle.com desires the use of your information for purposes exclusive of this privacy policy, you will be contacted for consent prior to its use. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data sent from a website and stored on the user's computer by the user's web browser while the user is browsing. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. 

We use web analytics services like Google Analytics. They may save cookies on your browser with the purpose of analyzing website performance and enhancing user experience. They are not linked to any personally identifiable information. We may use other types of local storage that function like cookies. Your browser may allow you to disable its local storage, disable cookies, delete the contents of its local storage or delete cookies. 

**Offsite Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that iBuzzle.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the sites to which we are linked. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of websites they visit. 

**Security**  
iBuzzle.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit personal information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-line. Personal information transmitted through our registration form is encrypted and protected with encryption software. 

**Registration**  
Although registration is not required for general use of our website, some areas like, submitting content on our website, do require registration. In order to complete the registration process, a user is required to provide their contact information. Contact information includes, name (first name and last name) and email id. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site. It is optional for the user to provide any additional information like, photograph, city, country and hobbies. 

**Surveys and Contests**  
On occasion, our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose their information. Information requested may include contact information and demographic information. Contest information, which includes contact and demographic information, is used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information is used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use of iBuzzle.com. 

**Special Offers/Updates**  
We send a welcoming email to all new members for the purpose of verifying their password and username. Members are given the choice to receive information on products, services, and special offers via email. Only those members opting-in will receive these emails. 

**Updating Personal Information/Member Status**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires the use of our service, we will provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data. 

**Notification of Policy Changes**  
Should our privacy policy change, notification will be posted on iBuzzle.com. 

If you have any questions or concerns about the collection of your information during your visit at iBuzzle.com, please contact us.
